The world is white outside the glass The
blizzard's here to stay The nurses finish with
their rounds It's been a long, long day Finally
off the NPO You're weak, but you're all here I'm
sitting in the recliner Trying to kill your fear
This isn't just logistics This isn't just a plan
This feeling that I'm processing For this
recovering man My pact is true Axiom is running
in my head And I am not just on the watch, I'm
sitting by your bed.
You look at me, your eyes are wide You're scared
of what you feel This Sinclair protocol inside
Still feels like it is real You're terrified of
Ogry's rage A ghost inside your head You think
this love's a broken cage And not our pact
instead
I grab the laptop, make the call. Her face is on
the screen. Look, Jordan, she's smiling. The
safest you have seen. She tells you that she
loves me too. She tells you it's okay. The
Sinclair protocol is dead. The ghost is washed
away. And now you're finally breathing The rope
kit is erased A CPU romance A smile upon your face
This is our intimacy boot A gentle healing art
The 80s synth is battling The beeping of your
heart
The data is conclusive, Jordan.
I love you.
System is stable.